http://nanohub.org/legal/privacy

Home › Legal › Privacy Policy
LegalAbuse PolicyPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseLicensing ContentCopyright InfringementAccessibility StatementVideo Authorization FormSubmitting ContentCreative CommonsGeneral Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy. We will not publicly disclose your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information without your permission. However; personally identifiable information, including your e-mail address, may be disclosed in the event of a business transaction such as a sale, merger, acquisition, or if we cease operations due to a lapse in funding.
We are a scientific project and we provide a free service, so we do track your activities on this site. We combine your usage metrics with others to create an aggregate picture of how the site is being used, and we report that usage publicly on our site and send similar quarterly reports to our program sponsors. However, such usage reports never contain detailed information about your activities as an individual without your prior consent.
From time to time, we work with other projects that seek to study social interactions on the site. We may share your activities with those groups, but they are bound by a Memorandum of Understanding to follow our policies and respect your privacy in the same way that we do. We may contact you on their behalf and ask you to participate in their study, but your participation is voluntary, and your information will not be publicly released without your prior consent.
We reserve the right to contact you to request additional information or to keep you updated on changes to nanoHUB.org. You may opt out of receiving newsletters and other non-essential communications by updating the settings in your account profile.
All resources, wiki articles, blogs, questions, answers, or other information posted or stored on nanoHUB.org is potentially available to all other users of nanoHUB.org. We do our best to restrict access to source code and to other private materials shared within groups. However, we are a research project and our software is constantly changing. We disclaim any responsibility or capability for the preservation of confidentiality of any information posted on this site. Do not post or store information on nanoHUB.org if you expect to or are obligated to protect the confidentiality of that information.
Changes to policy
We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you and/or prominently post notices of the changes on our website.
Search
Search
close search
